Guide to the Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center RG 42.5
New York University Archives
- Series II: Administrative Files, 1961-1988
  - Subseries D: Development, 1964-198
    - Life -- Insurance List, Circa 1979-1980 (Box II:13, Folder 28)
    - Life -- NEA, 1978-1979 (Box II:13, Folder 29)
    - Life -- NEA Application Resubmission, 1979-1980 (Box II:13, Folder 30)
    - Life -- Opening and Catalog, 1979 May-October (Box II:13, Folder 31)
    - Life -- PR Memos and Correspondence, 1979 March-July (Box II:13, Folder 32)
    - Life -- Press Photos Sent, 1979 March-July (Box II:13, Folder 33)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Claremont College, March 10-Apr. 13, 1980), 1979 July-1980 September (Box II:13, Folder 34)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Claremont College, March 10-Apr. 13, 1980), 1979 July (Box II:13, Folder 35)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Dartmouth Museum, Sept. 14-Nov. 2), 1979 June-July (Box II:13, Folder 36)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Dartmouth Museum, Sept. 14-Nov. 2), 1979 July (Box II:13, Folder 37)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Delaware Art Museum, OCt. 15-Dec. 2, 1979), 1979 May-December (Box II:13, Folder 38)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Doris O'Neil Correspondence), 1978 November-1980 December (Box II:13, Folder 39)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Exeter Academy, May 15-June 15, 1981), 1981 March-July (Box II:13, Folder 40)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Exeter Academy, May 15-June 15, 1981), 1979 July (Box II:13, Folder 41)
    - Life -- Traveling Show Fact Sheets, Circa 1979-1981 (Box II:13, Folder 42)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Keene State College, Aug. 31-Sept. 28, 1980), 1979-1981 (Box II:13, Folder 43)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Keene State College, Aug. 31-Sept. 28, 1980), 1979-1981 (Box II:13, Folder 44)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Lufkin Historical, Texas), 1979 July-November (Box II:13, Folder 45)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Lufkin Historical, Texas), 1979 July-August (Box II:13, Folder 46)
    - Lilfe -- Traveling Show (Minnesota May-June 22, 1980), 1979 October-1980 October (Box II:13, Folder 47)
    - Lilfe -- Traveling Show (Minnesota May-June 22, 1980), 1979 December-1980 July (Box II:13, Folder 48)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Notre Dame, Oct. - Nov., 1981), 1980 Janaury-February (Box II:13, Folder 49)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Notre Dame, Oct.-Nov., 1981), 1980 February-March (Box II:13, Folder 50)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (St. Louis, March-May 2, 1981), 1979 November-1981 April (Box II:13, Folder 51)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (St. Louis, March-May 2, 1981), 1979 November (Box II:13, Folder 52)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Transportation), 1979 March-December (Box II:13, Folder 53)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Valparaiso University, Jan. 15-Feb. 25, 1980), 1978-1980 March (Box II:13, Folder 54)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Vancouver, July-Aug. 24, 1980), 1979 September-1980 October (Box II:13, Folder 55)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Vancouver, July-Aug. 24, 1980), 1979 November (Box II:13, Folder 56)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (University of Pittsburgh, Jan. 1-Feb 28, 1981), 1979 August-1981 March (Box II:13, Folder 57)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (University of Pittsburgh, Jan. 1-Feb 28, 1981), 1979 September-1981 March (Box II:13, Folder 58)
    - Life -- Traveling Show (Wheelabrator Frye), 1979 May-1980 July (Box II:13, Folder 59)
    - American Painting -- Barbara Rose Catalogue Sales, 1979 September-December (Box II:13, Folder 60)
    - American Painting -- Gary Reynold's File, 1979 June-October (Box II:13, Folder 61)
    - American Painting -- New York Council on the Humanities, 1979 June-August (Box II:13, Folder 62)
    - American Painting -- Photographs Sent Out, 1979 September-1980 March (Box II:13, Folder 63)
    - American Painting -- SCM Corporation, 1979 June-September (Box II:13, Folder 64)
    - American Painting -- Symposium, 1979 July-October (Box II:13, Folder 65)
    - American Symbolist -- Budget, 1976 December-1979 June (Box II:13, Folder 66)
    - American Symbolist -- Funding, 1977 December-1979 October (Box II:13, Folder 67)
    - American Symbolist -- Loan Rejections, 1978 Janaury-1979 April (Box II:13, Folder 68)
    - American Symbolist -- Loan Rejects, 1979 April-October (Box II:13, Folder 69)
    - American Symbolist -- Loan Requests (1 of 2), 1977 December-1978 March (Box II:13, Folder 70)
    - American Symbolist -- Loan Requests (2 of 2), 1977 December-1978 February (Box II:13, Folder 71)
    - American Symbolist -- Loans (1 of 2), 1977 December-1978 February (Box II:13, Folder 72)
    - American Symbolist -- Loans (2 of 2), 1977 December-1978 February (Box II:13, Folder 73)
    - American Symbolist -- Lenders A-L (1 of 2), 1979 April-1980 June (Box II:13, Folder 74)
    - American Symbolist -- Lenders A-L (2 of 2), 1979 April-October (Box II:13, Folder 75)
    - American Symbolist -- Lenders M-Z (1 of 2), 1979 March-1980 January (Box II:13, Folder 76)
    - American Symbolist -- Lenders M-Z (2 of 2), 1979 April-1980 January (Box II:13, Folder 77)
    - American Symbolist -- Insurance, 1979 August-1980 February (Box II:14, Folder 1)
    - American Symbolist -- Insurance, 1979 September-October (Box II:14, Folder 2)
    - American Symbolist -- Shipping Arrangements, 1979 September-December (Box II:14, Folder 3)
    - American Symbolist -- Travel and Financial, 1977 December-1978 November (Box II:14, Folder 4)
    - Charles Gleyre -- Auxiliary Fund, 1979 July-1980 April (Box II:14, Folder 5)
    - Charles Gleyre -- Funding, 1976 December-1980 March (Box II:14, Folder 6)
    - Charles Gleyre -- Invitations, 1978 December-1979 December (Box II:14, Folder 7)
    - Charles Gleyre -- Auxillary Loans, 1979 November-1980 September (Box II:14, Folder 8)
    - Charles Gleyre -- Boston Loan, 1977 October-1980 January (Box II:14, Folder 9)
    - Charles Gleyre -- Licht Collection Loan, 1979 October-1980 June (Box II:14, Folder 10)
    - Charles Gleyre -- Musee Cantonal Loans, 1978 March-1980 January (Box II:14, Folder 11)
    - Charles Gleyre -- Musee Cantonal Loans, 1979 February-December (Box II:14, Folder 12)
    - Charles Gleyre -- NEA Grant Accepted (1977-1980), 1977 January-1981 May (Box II:14, Folder 13)
    - Charles Gleyre -- Tour (Busch-Reisinger Museum), 1976 November-1981 April (Box II:14, Folder 14)
    - Charles Gleyre -- Tour (Cleveland Museum of Art), 1978 August-1979 March (Box II:14, Folder 15)
    - Charles Gleyre -- Tour (University of Maryland), 1979 (Box II:14, Folder 16)
    - Charles Gleyre -- Transportation and Insurance, 1977 January-1980 March (Box II:14, Folder 17)
    - Charles Gleyre -- Transportation and Insurance, 1979 December (Box II:14, Folder 18)
    - Art in NYC in 1950s and 1960s -- NEA Grant, 1979-1980 (Box II:14, Folder 19)
    - New Choreography -- Dance Evenings (January 16-17, 1980), 1979 December-1980 January (Box II:14, Folder 20)
    - Grey Gallery Budget (1 of 2), 1980 (Box II:14, Folder 21)
    - Grey Gallery Budget (2 of 2), 1980 (Box II:14, Folder 22)
    - David Hickney -- Benefit, 1980 April-September (Box II:14, Folder 23)
    - David Hockney -- Agreement, 1977 December-1980 March (Box II:14, Folder 24)
    - David Hockney -- Roxy Benefit Correspondence, 1980 February-September (Box II:14, Folder 25)
    - David Hockney -- Petersburg Press Inc. and Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1979 August-1981 August (Box II:14, Folder 26)
    - David Hockney -- Petersburg Press Inc. and Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1980 April (Box II:14, Folder 27)
    - American Stereographs -- Loans and Insurance, 1980 April-July (Box II:14, Folder 28)
    - American Stereographs -- Contract, 1979 January-1980 April (Box II:14, Folder 29)
    - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Correspondence, 1979 February-1981 September (Box II:14, Folder 30)
    - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Auxiliary (Financial), 1980 July-September (Box II:14, Folder 31)
    - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Financial, 1980 June-September (Box II:14, Folder 32)
    - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Funding, 1977 March-1980 May (Box II:14, Folder 33)
    - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Funding Letters, 1979 January-February (Box II:14, Folder 34)
    - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Insurance, 1980 June-July (Box II:14, Folder 35)
    - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Lenders, 1980 March-October (Box II:14, Folder 36)
    - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- NEA Grant, 1976 July-1981 June (Box II:14, Folder 37)
    - Perceiving Modern Sculpture -- Transportation, 1980 June-September (Box II:14, Folder 38)
    - Sheldon Levison -- Correspondence, 1980 February-1982 March (Box II:14, Folder 39)
    - Sheldon Levison -- Receipts and Other Miscellaneous, 1979 November-1980 October (Box II:14, Folder 40)
    - Walter Gay -- Lenders A-L (1 of 2), 1978 February-1980 December (Box II:14, Folder 41)
    - Walter Gay -- Lenders A-L (2 of 2), 1978 March-1980 November (Box II:14, Folder 42)
    - Walter Gay -- Lenders M-Z (1 of 2), 1978 February-1981 January (Box II:14, Folder 43)
    - Walter Gay -- Lenders M-Z (2 of 2), 1978 February-1980 December (Box II:14, Folder 44)
    - Walter Gay -- Extension of Exhibition Letters, 1980 July (Box II:14, Folder 45)
    - Walter Gay -- Loans Rejected, 1978 February-1980 September (Box II:14, Folder 46)
    - Walter Gay -- Correspondence, 1979 September-1980 October (Box II:15, Folder 1)
    - Walter Gay -- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1980 September-1981 September (Box II:15, Folder 2)
    - Walter Gay -- Funding, 1980 June-1988 December (Box II:15, Folder 3)
    - Walter Gay -- Insurance and Transportation, 1980 August-November (Box II:15, Folder 4)
    - Walter Gay -- NEA Grant 1979-1980 Accepted, 1979 February-1981 July (Box II:15, Folder 5)
    - Walter Gay -- NEA Grant 1980, 1978 March-1980 November (Box II:15, Folder 6)
    - Walter Gay -- NEA Grant 1980-1981 Implementation, 1980 March-April (Box II:15, Folder 7)
    - Janson Reception (Nov. 24, 1980) (Box II:15, Folder 8)
    - New York Design Fair -- Designer's Saturday (October 11), 1979 July-1980 December (Box II:15, Folder 9)
    - Sonia Delaunay -- Contract, 1980 February-March (Box II:15, Folder 10)
    - Sonia Delaunay -- Correspondence, 1978 November-1980 December (Box II:15, Folder 11)
    - Sonia Delaunay -- Crate List, 1980 (Box II:15, Folder 12)
    - Sonia Delaunay -- Crate Lists, etc., 1980-1981 (Box II:15, Folder 13)
    - Sonia Delaunay -- Financial, 1980 August-1981 March (Box II:15, Folder 14)
    - Sonia Delaunay -- Funding, 1978 December-1980 November (Box II:15, Folder 15)
    - Sonia Delaunay -- Grant, 1980 (Box II:15, Folder 16)
    - Court of Benin -- Correspondence, 1979 August-1981 April (Box II:15, Folder 17)
    - Court of Benin -- Grant, 1979 June-1980 September (Box II:15, Folder 18)
    - Court of Benin -- Insurance, 1979 December-1981 February (Box II:15, Folder 19)
    - Court of Benin -- Loan Forms, 1980 January-1981 March (Box II:15, Folder 20)
    - Court of Benin -- Various Issues with Exhibit, 1980 June-1981 February (Box II:15, Folder 21)
    - Italian Drawings -- Contract and Loans, 1980 February-1981 April (Box II:15, Folder 22)
    - Italian Drawings -- Correspondence, 1981 January-March (Box II:15, Folder 23)
    - Italian Drawings -- Funding, 1980 December-1981 January (Box II:15, Folder 24)
    - Italian Drawings -- Special Events, Symposium, etc., 1980 November-1981 May (Box II:15, Folder 25)
    - Tracking the Marvelous -- Lenders (1 of 2), 1980 November-1981 June (Box II:15, Folder 26)
    - Tracking the Marvelous -- Lenders (2 of 2), 1980 November-1983 March (Box II:15, Folder 27)
    - Tracking the Marvelous -- Funding, 1980 October-1981 February (Box II:15, Folder 28)
    - Tracking the Marvelous -- Auxiliary, 1981 April-August (Box II:15, Folder 29)
    - Tracking the Marvelous -- Financial, 1980 March-1982 March (Box II:15, Folder 30)
    - Tracking the Marvelous -- Loans Rejected, 1980 November-1981 May (Box II:15, Folder 31)
    - Tracking the Marvelous -- Insurance and Transportation, 1981 April-June (Box II:15, Folder 32)
    - Tracking the Marvelous -- Myers May 11, 1981 Benefit Correspondence, 1981 February-April (Box II:15, Folder 33)
    - Tracking the Marvelous -- Opening Dinner, 1981 January-April (Box II:15, Folder 34)
    - Tracking the Marvelous -- Symposium (May 5, 1981), 1981 February (Box II:15, Folder 35)
    - Space Photography -- Correspondence, 1979 December-1982 June (Box II:15, Folder 36)
    - Space Photography -- Financial, 1980 September-1981 June (Box II:15, Folder 37)
    - Space Photography -- Funding (1 of 2), 1980 March-1982 June (Box II:15, Folder 38)
    - Space Photography -- Funding (2 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box II:15, Folder 39)
    - Space Photography -- Insurance and Transportation, 1980 September-1982 February (Box II:15, Folder 40)
    - Space Photography -- Space Photography -- Loan Requests, 1980 February-1981 May (Box II:15, Folder 41)
    - Space Photography -- Richard Maurer Auxillary Loans, 1980 July-1985 November (Box II:15, Folder 42)
    - Space Photography -- Richard Maurer Auxillary Loans, 1981 June (Box II:15, Folder 43)
    - Space Photography -- Motorola Sponsorship, 1981 May-December (Box II:15, Folder 44)
    - Space Photography -- NEA Grant 1980-1981, 1979 December-1982 January (Box II:15, Folder 45)
    - Space Photography -- NEA Grant Implementation 1981-1982, 1980 August-1981 September (Box II:15, Folder 46)
    - Space Photography -- Travel, 1981 March-1982 May (Box II:15, Folder 47)
    - Space Photography -- Travel (Science Museum, London), 1981 February-1983 January (Box II:15, Folder 48)
    - Space Photography -- Travel (Science Museum of VA), 1983 January-October (Box II:15, Folder 49)
    - Space Photography -- Travel (Royal Ontario Museum), 1981 January-1983 April (Box II:15, Folder 50)
    - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Andre Kertesz, 1981 August-October (Box II:15, Folder 51)
    - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Correspondence, 1981 May-August (Box II:15, Folder 52)
    - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Correspondence (Box II:15, Folder 52)
    - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Inagural Madallion/Convocation, 1981 February-October (Box II:15, Folder 53)
    - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Invitation, 1981 (Box II:15, Folder 54)
    - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- NYU Callendar, 1980 September-1982 June (Box II:15, Folder 55)
    - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Ralph Fasanella, 1981 August-1982 May (Box II:15, Folder 56)
    - Tanya Grosman -- Dinner, 1981 April-June (Box II:15, Folder 57)
    - Tanya Grosman -- Dinner Receipts and Checks Deposited, 1981 (Box II:15, Folder 58)
    - Tanya Grosman -- Loans, 1981 April-July (Box II:15, Folder 59)
    - Krasner/Pollock -- Book and Reproduction Requests, 1981 June-1982 August (Box II:16, File 1)
    - Krasner/Pollock -- Correspondence, 1979 March-1982 April (Box II:16, File 2)
    - Krasner/Pollock -- Damages to Pollock No. 6 (Houston), 1981 September-1982 October (Box II:16, File 3)
    - Krasner/Pollock -- Funding, 1980 July-1981 July (Box II:16, File 4)
    - Krasner/Pollock -- Guild Hall Agreement, 1981 February (Box II:16, File 5)
    - Krasner/Pollock -- Guild Hall Information, 1981-1982 March (Box II:16, File 6)
    - Krasner/Pollock -- Krasner Dinner, 1981 October-November (Box II:16, File 7)
    - Krasner/Pollock -- Krasner-Novack Video Interview, 1979 October-1984 July (Box II:16, File 8)
    - Krasner/Pollock -- Loan Requests (Grey Only), 1981 June-1982 January (Box II:16, File 9)
    - Krasner/Pollock -- Loans Rejected, 1981 May-July (Box II:16, File 10)
    - Krasner/Pollock -- Loan Requests, 1981 May-November (Box II:16, File 11)
    - Krasner/Pollock -- NEA (1980-1981), 1979-1981 (Box II:16, File 12)
    - Krasner/Pollock -- NEA Implementation (1981-1982), 1981 March-September (Box II:16, File 13)
    - Krasner/Pollock -- NEA (1980-1981), CIrca 1980-1981 (Box II:16, File 14)
    - Krasner/Pollock -- People to Invite, CIrca 1980-1981 (Box II:16, File 15)
    - Krasner/Pollock -- Symposium, 1981 November-December (Box II:16, File 16)
    - Krasner/Pollock -- Transportation from Guild Hall, 1981 April-1982 June (Box II:16, File 17)
    - Krasner/Pollock -- Transportation from Guild Hall, 1980 November-1981 November (Box II:16, File 18)
    - Judson Dance Theater - Correspondence and Other Miscellaneous, 1981 December-1982 November (Box II:16, File 19)
    - Judson Dance Theater - Loan Forms and Receipts, 1982 January-1984 May (Box II:16, File 20)
    - Judson Dance Theater - NEA Grant (Judson Church With Bennington College 1980-1981), 1979-1980 (Box II:16, File 21)
    - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Correspondence (1 of 2), 1976 October-1982 February (Box II:16, File 22)
    - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Correspondence (2 of 2), 1981 November-1983 October (Box II:16, File 23)
    - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Correspondence (Notes), Circa 1980-1983 (Box II:16, File 24)
    - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- NEA Grant (1980-1981), 1978 March-1982 April (Box II:16, File 25)
    - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Funding (1 of 2), 1981 January-1982 November (Box II:16, File 26)
    - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Funding (2 of 2), 1981 (Box II:16, File 27)
    - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Burra Loan Forms Returned (1 of 2), 1981 November-1982 August (Box II:16, File 28)
    - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Burra Loan Forms Returned (2 of 2), 1981 May-1982 May (Box II:16, File 29)
    - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Nash Loan Forms Returned (1 of 2), 1981-1982 (Box II:16, File 30)
    - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Nash Loan Forms Returned (2 of 2), 1981-1982 (Box II:16, File 31)
    - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Nash Loans Rejected, 1981 November-1982 November (Box II:16, File 32)
    - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Nash Loans Rejected, 1981-1982 (Box II:16, File 33)
    - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Burra Works Requested, 1981 November-December (Box II:16, File 34)
    - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Insurance, 1982 February (Box II:16, File 35)
    - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Export and Import Papers, 1982 January-April (Box II:16, File 36)
    - Burra and Nash (3 British Painters) -- Insurance and Transportation, 1982 January-May (Box II:16, File 37)
    - Audubon -- Exhibition Lenders A-L (1 of 2), 1981-1982 (Box II:3, Folder 19)
    - Audubon -- Exhibition Lenders A-L (2 of 2), 1981-1982 (Box II:3, Folder 20)
    - Audubon -- Exhibition Lenders M-Z (1 of 3), 1981-1982 (Box II:3, Folder 21)
    - Audubon -- Exhibition Lenders M-Z (2 of 3), 1981-1982 (Box II:3, Folder 22)
    - Audubon -- Exhibition Lenders M-Z (3 of 3), 1981-1982 (Box II:3, Folder 23)
    - Audubon -- Loans Rejected, 1981-1982 (Box II:3, Folder 24)
    - Audubon -- NEH Grant Application - Implementation, 1981 March-September (Box II:3, Folder 25)
    - Audubon -- Grant, 1981 March (Box II:3, Folder 26)
    - Audubon -- Insurance, 1982 March-May (Box II:3, Folder 27)
    - Audubon -- Catalog, 1982 April-July (Box II:3, Folder 28)
    - Audubon -- Funding, 1981 December-1982 August (Box II:3, Folder 29)
    - Around the Square -- Grant, 1981 February-1983 March (Box II:3, Folder 30)
    - Around the Square -- Funding, 1982 February-July (Box II:3, Folder 31)
    - Around the Square -- Finances, 1982 April-June (Box II:3, Folder 32)
    - Around the Square -- AARS Loan, 1982 June 10-August 31 (Box II:3, Folder 33)
    - Morse -- Lenders A-L, 1981 February-1982 November (Box II:3, Folder 34)
    - Morse -- Lenders M-Z (1 of 2), 1981 February-1982 December (Box II:3, Folder 35)
    - Morse -- Lenders M-Z (2 of 2), 1981 February-1982 December (Box II:4, Folder 1)
    - Samuel F. B. Morse Funding -- Private Sources, 1980 November-1983 June (Box II:4, Folder 2)
    - Morse -- Catalogue Production, 1982 July-1983 January (Box II:4, Folder 3)
    - Morse -- Loans Rejected, 1981 March-1982 September (Box II:4, Folder 4)
    - Morse -- Auxillary Loans, 1982 July-1983 April (Box II:4, Folder 5)
    - Morse -- Insurance and Shipping, 1982 July-September (Box II:4, Folder 6)
    - Mapplethrope, Robert, 1981 May-1982 December (Box II:4, Folder 7)
    - Coplans, John, 1982 September-1983 February (Box II:4, Folder 8)
    - Coupon, Will, 1982 September-1983 June (Box II:4, Folder 9)
    - Crampton, Nancy, 1982 September-1984 July (Box II:4, Folder 10)
    - Goldin, Nan, 1982 September-1983 January (Box II:4, Folder 11)
    - Heister, Scott, 1982 September-1983 January (Box II:4, Folder 12)
    - Hockney, David, 1982 October-1984 April (Box II:4, Folder 13)
    - Hujar, Peter, 1982 September-1983 January (Box II:4, Folder 14)
    - McGowan, Kenneth, 1982 January-November (Box II:4, Folder 15)
    - Ricatto, Cosimo Di Leo, 1982 September-1983 January (Box II:4, Folder 16)
    - Seidner, David, 1982 September-1983 October (Box II:4, Folder 17)
    - Sherman, Cindy, 1982 September-1983 January (Box II:4, Folder 18)
    - Springs, Alice, 1982 January-1983 January (Box II:4, Folder 19)
    - Weber, Bruce, 1982 September-1983 January (Box II:4, Folder 20)
    - Winokur, Neil, 1982 September-1983 January (Box II:4, Folder 21)
    - Wegman, William, 1982 October-1983 February (Box II:4, Folder 22)
    - Faces Photographed, 1982 October (Box II:4, Folder 23)
    - Turkish Exhibition -- AXIA, 1982 October-1983 December (Box II:4, Folder 24)
    - Turkish Loans, Transportation, Insurance, etc., 1982 October-1983 July (Box II:4, Folder 25)
    - Turkish Exhibitions -- Additional Loans, 1983 January-July (Box II:4, Folder 26)
    - Kahlo/Modotti Funding, 1982 March-1983 July (Box II:4, Folder 27)
    - Kohlo/Modotti Pending Lenders, 1982 July-1983 April (Box II:4, Folder 28)
    - Francis Returns (Kahlo/Modotti), 1983 April (Box II:4, Folder 29)
    - Pandolfi Returns (Kahlo/Modotti), 1983 (Box II:4, Folder 30)
    - Kahlo -- Additional Loans Responses (1 of 2), 1981 December-1987 May (Box II:4, Folder 31)
    - Kahlo -- Additional Loans Responses (2 of 2), 1981 December-1987 May (Box II:4, Folder 32)
    - Kahlo/Modotti -- 1982 NEA Grant (Box II:4, Folder 33)
    - Kahlo/Modotti -- Transportation and Insurance, 1983 January-May (Box II:4, Folder 34)
    - Two Installations - Correspondence, 1982 April-November (Box II:4, Folder 35)
    - Elgort, Arthur, 1983 January 12 (Box II:4, Folder 36)
    - Outerbridge -- Insurance, 1983 September-October (Box II:4, Folder 37)
    - Paul Outerbridge -- Transportation, 1983 September-October (Box II:4, Folder 38)
    - Outerbridge -- Release Letters of 2 Prints, 1983 October (Box II:4, Folder 39)
    - Outerbridge -- Condition Report, 1983 July-October (Box II:4, Folder 40)
    - Paul Outerbridge -- Correspondence, 1982 May-1984 April (Box II:4, Folder 41)
    - Condition Reports, 1982 August-1985 March (Box II:4, Folder 42)
    - Eva Hesse Drawings -- 1983, 1980 October-1983 February (Box II:4, Folder 43)
    - Eva Hesse -- Additional Sculpture, 1982 October-1983 July (Box II:4, Folder 44)
    - Bergdorf/Montana -- Correspondence, 1983 February-July (Box II:4, Folder 45)
    - Louis Dahl-Wolfe -- Loan Form, 1983 September (Box II:4, Folder 46)
    - Picasso -- Loans Rejected, 1983 June 10 (Box II:4, Folder 47)
    - Picasso -- Funding, 1982 February-1984 March (Box II:4, Folder 48)
    - Picasso -- NEA Grant, 1982 July-1984 January (Box II:4, Folder 49)
    - Picasso -- Correspondence with Schiff, 1982 July-1983 April (Box II:4, Folder 50)
    - Picasso -- Correspondence, 1982 July-1984 February (Box II:4, Folder 51)
    - Picasso -- Guggenheim, 1983 December-1984 January (Box II:4, Folder 52)
    - Picasso -- Japan, 1983 August-November (Box II:4, Folder 53)
    - Picasso -- Braziller Contract, 1983 August-1984 August (Box II:4, Folder 54)
    - Picasso -- Budget, 1983 October 27 (Box II:4, Folder 55)